- +91 7770077872
- https://aboutav.vercel.app/ avanishv73@gmail.com

9 CONTACT ME

A/504, Kailash Heights, Agarwal Circle, Vasai East, Mumbai, Maharashtra.

EDUCATION

PATKAR COLLEGE, GOREGAON

MASTERS IN MSCIT, CGPA - 9.0 2021 - 2023

VIVA COLLEGE, VIRAR

GRADUATE IN BSCIT, CGPA - 8.0 2018 - 2021

INTERMEDIATE (HSC), COMMERCE

PERCENTAGE- 76% (MH STATE BOARD) YEAR OF COMPLETION: 2017

SECONDARY (SSC)

PERCENTAGE- 87% (MH STATE BOARD) YEAR OF COMPLETION: 2015

SKILLS

HTML, CSS, JAVASCRIPT, BOOTSTRAP, JQUERY WORDPRESS, SHOPIFY, PHP, MYSQL

AVANISH R. VISHWAKARMA

FRONT END WEB DEVELOPER

ABOUT ME

I have completed my Masters Degree from Patkar Varde College, Goregaon (Mumbai University) with 9.0 CGPA in March 2023.I had worked with Markweb Solutions as a FrontEnd Web Developer for 9 months after that i switched to Digital Vasai in Feb 2024.

JOB EXPERIENCE

WEB DEVELOPER

Feb 2024 - Present

Digital Vasai, Vasai

Currently i am working as a WordPress Developer in Digital Vasai, Where my role is to design, develop and maintain the wordpress website from scratch.I design cool websites, make sure they work perfectly, and if any bugs or issues pop up, I'm on it to fix them up. Basically, I'm here to make sure your website looks great and runs smoothly without any hiccups.

FRONT END DEVELOPER

May 2023 - Jan 2024

Markweb Solutions, Borivali

As a WordPress Developer, I have had the privilege of working at Markweb Solutions. Where i have Worked on Wordpress, Shopify as well as Webflow.

WEB DEVELOPER INTERN

Feb 2023

NextGen Lab, Patkar College

This was a 1 month Web Development Internship Provided at NextGen Lab provided By Patkar Varde College, Goregaon during Pursuing Masters in (MscIT).

PROJECTS

https://aligner32.com/

https://alignerco.com/

https://alignerco.ca/

https://smilepath.com.au/

https://codeaamy.com/

https://suvidya.ac.in/

https://shloka700.com/

https://alainstore.in/

https://moneeyacademy.com/

https://timbercheese.com/

https://vasaivirarnews.com/

https://digitalvasai.com/

https://ramashary.com/

https://janyutech.com/